

NAO SAMNANG

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Nationality : Cambodia

Sex : Male

Date of Birth :17/March/2002

Place of Birth : Oddor Mean Chei

Province

Status : Single

CONTACT

Address : TUEK L'AK TI2;

Phnom Penh.

Phone Number : 068 809 810

Email : nangzk70@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Khmer : Mother Tongue

English : Medium

Thai : A little

SUMMARY ABOUT ME

I used to have work experience in a shop and the real estate company in **Digital marketing** and **social media**; but my job doesn't match the skills I learned. so I need to look for a job in Web Developer to gain experience in this job. Therefore, I promise myself I will work hard to get good results for myself and the company.

EDUCATION BACKROUND

2020-2024 : National University of Management

2017-2020 : AnLong Veng High School

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018-19 : Assistant Teacher at Computer & English

2020-2021 : Work at The Mart

2022-2023 : Digital Marketing

Now : Digital Marketing & Social media

KNOWLEDGE AND SKILL

Computer : Microsoft Office (word; Excel; Power

Point).

Program : JAVA; PHP; HTML; CSS; C#; SQL;

JAVASCRIPT.

Design : Figma; Photoshop(basic).

Other: Setup software; Internet; Email &

Researching.

PERSONAL STRENGTH

I am very hard working and self-motivated and interpersonal skills. My key strengths include:

- ❖ Good communication.
- * Team work and creative.
- Honest,
- Confidence